Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Tell me.
Beys!
Alps!
Why would someone going to
a conquest be sad?
It's because we are ashamed, my bey.
We didn't trust you.
We believed the plot against Turgut Bey.
We regret it.
Which regret is this?
Which hesitation is this?
If you don't take lessons from
the past...
how will you look into the future?
Our target is Yenişehir.
İznik!
And Bursa!
But...
with those who don't trust the leader,
you can't reach anywhere.
With those who don't listen to the bey,
you can't conquer anything.
If anyone doubts the gray wolf again,
may our swords turn red with our blood!
This is the last.
We follow your decisions, Osman Bey.
Think me as your arrow.
I go wherever you
release me to.
Say strike and we'll strike.
Barkın's end is a lesson to us, my bey.
Turgut Bey, give us your blessing.
It's yours.
Let's not repeat it.
Don't throw a wolf of yours to
the jackals because of slander.
One calamity is better than
a thousand pieces of advice.
But forgiving won't do.
Those who have the heart
should follow us...
if you don't have the heart...
stay back.
I've listened to many tales on
these lands.
Many of them were telling how Osman
turned into a great bey from a young man.
And a few of them were telling about
the heroism of the lords.
But every tale has an end.
And Osman's ends here.
If Osman ends...
so will the Turks.
Osman chose here as a quarter,
Commander Romanos.
It's wide and open.
Close to assaults.
What kind of an attack
will bring this end?
Do you know what he told me?
-If you want to ambush a wolf...
-You must be smarter.
I'm smarter than him.
Right.
This place is well-protected.
But this is why he won't expect
an ambush here.
Great soldiers of the Rome!
Osman who spilled your blood...
who took your lands...
who stole your property...
will be here soon!
Is his grave ready?
It is!
I prepared a beautiful trap for them.
Yenişehir
Come on, brothers!
It's the day of jihad!
-Allah is eternal!
-Allah is righteous!
We'll hang on until Osman Bey
comes, inshallah!
Are the warriors training in
İnegöl ready, Turgut Bey?
Mashallah to all of them.
To not get spotted...
they are divided in Yılanlık.
Thank you.
-Boran.
-My bey.
Close all the roads.
No caravan will go to Yenişehir.
As my bey orders.
Konur, alps will position here.
Set the tent here.
As you order, my bey.
Come on!
Who is this brother?
See him as you see me, my bey.
It's Koygan.
I came with the envoy
but didn't return.
I follow the righteous path, my bey.
I wish to be under your command.
Thank you.
Our doors are open to anyone
who's heart is beating with us.
-Welcome.
-Thank you, my bey.
Let's check around.
Let's be sure of where we stand.
With the name of Allah.
Come on.
Hold there, old men!
Where?
I'll take your heathen head with
my sword!
You are surrounded.
Lower your swords.
Kumral.
Being a martyr is sweet but...
dying away from home
hurts me.
Hold there, Master Davud.
Maybe these lands will turn into
home before we die!
Inshallah.
Inshallah!
It's harmful to dream this much
at this age, old men.
You all will die.
And Rome will always be here.
Demon. You will die first.
-Then, Allah is eternal!
-Allah is righteous!
My God, protect them!
Alps!
Shield wall!
Hang on!
Hang on, alps!
Look at them!
Romanos!
Come here!
Alps! Attack!
Wait.
Who are you?
Where are you from?
We are from İznik.
We came to support you in
your war against the Turks.
We brought provisions
for the people...
and medicine for the physicians.
I thought you were informed.
We sent the news before
moving out.
Welcome. We'll still search
as a caution.
Soldiers! We'll search the carts.
Get down.
We'll search.
We brought provisions.
The people of İznik sent it for
the people of Yenişehir.
We took a long way here.
We are tired.
But if you want so,
let's get down.
Soldier!
Our guests from İznik?
Yes, sir.
You fools!
Is this how you treat people
helping you?
Leave the carts and
get inside.
Yes, commander.
Welcome. Please.
Let them pass.
We are grateful, commander.
You'll find Kumral Abdal.
Boran.
Allahu Akbar!
Romanos!
Will we be captives
in the hands of the infidels?
Like Prophet Joseph.
If our destiny is a dungeon,
we appreciate it too.
But this heart wants to die in a battle
for Allah, not in a dungeon.
The infidel's chain
isn't enough for us.
Then, Allah is eternal!
Allah is righteous!
If you try to run again,
I won't be kind.
Take them.
To the horses!
If you fight with a wolf,
you'll fight to the death.
Where are you running to?
It's enough of you Turks!
Come.
We lost our way.
But we die on the right way.
There is--
You fought to the death.
Soldiers, come on!
We have many martyrs, my bey.
Boran.
They knew the way of jihad.
This way leads to martyrdom.
But it's haram to breathe for those
who take our breath.
Musa Bey.
You walked to martyrdom too.
Alps.
We'll take Yenişehir.
The names of those who've fallen for
it will be remembered in that city.
Let's do our final duty.
Open the gate!
Commander Romanos is coming!
I hope it's good.
Be cautious.
Close the gates!
I don't want any holes!
Increase the guards!
Turks are coming!
This will be their grave!
Come with me!
Romanos got away from
Osman Bey.
How did he survive
all the traps?
It would be good to kill him.
It's getting complicated.
After Aygül comes, we'll
find out what's happening.
-It's not good.
-What's happening?
Where is the smith?
Akça Dervish, Kumral Abdal, the Smith;
they are all caught.
Romanos' soldiers got them.
They took them to
the dungeon.
What will we do now?
Now.
What we'll do is very simple.
You'll tell me what
you were doing.
We won't tell anything.
I'm asking again. Your Osman Bey.
Why did he send you?
Alright. You won't speak.
Don't speak. I'll figure it out
anyway.
Our warriors have fallen
for the conquest.
They've fallen, fighting chest to
chest against the heathens.
Musa Bey and his alps.
They'll always be in our hearts.
Romanos has the numbers, Osman Bey.
They could've let them pass.
But the lions fought.
May they rest in heaven.
They burned our hearts.
We'll burn them with that fire.
Now, we won't stop until taking
Yenişehir.
We won't sheathe our weapons until
raising Islam's banner there.
My bey, as you ordered,
the women sneaked into Yenişehir.
Firstly, we'll speak.
If they don't hear...
they'll hear the sounds
of our weapons.
Alps, we are going to our future city
from the hill of martyrs.
Come on.
Romanos is in the castle.
Heknows that Kumral Abdal snuck in.
We'll be more cautious now.
We have to save them before
our mission then.
Mashallah, Cerkutay.
I'm telling you. Mother Selcan gave her
honey years ago and it worked now!
But I didn't do the job.
Kumral Abdal did.
He left this to Priest Hristo.
Good.
We'll save him with the map
he found.
The dungeon is here.
Firstly, to enter the dungeon,
we must learn the soldier count.
Let's divide labor.
Some of us will search for them.
The rest will take positions.
Cerkutay, check the dungeon
and the corridors.
We should know how many
soldiers are there.
Aygül, talk to the sisters.
They should blend into the people.
No one should suspect anything.
Don't worry, they'll walk on the snow
but leave no trace.
Come on, Cerkutay.
Is this how you'll carry
that shield?
Is this how you'll protect the lands
against Turkish arrows?
I'm asking you?
This is how you hold a shield!
-Go and hang him!
-No, sir!
I want to die fighting.
Not for nothing.
Then carry the shield worthy of
a Roman soldier!
Because if you don't...
we all will die today.
We all will die!
Turks killed everyone in İnegöl and
Bilecik...
who refused to be slaves.
Women, priests, children...
they stole properties...
they burned churches,
they destroyed stores!
The dead are gone...
the remaining are slaves.
But I won't allow this.
Your emperor is with you!
He sent me to protect you.
Don't be afraid of the Turks!
Commander Romanos!
Osman Bey wishes to speak to you, sir.
He'll want me to surrender the city.
-What will we do?
-Spread my words here.
They should afraid of the Turks
like monsters.
Invite them to resistance.
I need to recruit everyone now.
-I'll do what it takes.
-So will I.
I'll talk to Osman.
When you were holding İnegöl
with Nikola...
I sent you Darius' head.
I took Nikola's head in front
of your eyes.
And now, the traitor Barkın's head.
See his fate.
And know who's next.
So, my head it at the tip
of your sword, huh?
It's not important.
What's important is the security
of the people of Yenişehir.
Give me Yenişehir in peace.
Neither your soldiers nor the civilians
should get hurt.
The elders of the city, the commanders...
I can't decide on that alone.
And also, how can I trust you?
When did we ever dishonor
our word?
Give me Yenişehir and no one
will get hurt.
Alright.
Give me some time.
I'll try to convince them.
I give you time until tomorrow.
Don't hold anything back.
But when the words are over...
the swords will speak.
Come on!
Yenişehir
They are protecting the dungeon well.
There are two corridors to there and
both are filled with soldiers.
Did you see Kumral Abdal and
Master Davud?
They don't let anyone in.
I couldn't pass through
the first corridor.
If we enter now...
we can't leave silently.
We'll put the conquest at risk.
Then, we'll wait for Osman Bey.
As the war breaks,
we'll use the chaos to enter the dungeon.
What if they come late?
Maybe we should enter now.
We can't do it silently, Ayşe Hatun.
Or we all will die.
If they wanted to kill,
they wouldn't put them in the dungeon.
They'll interrogate them.
As we talked before,
we should get prepared.
When the time comes, we'll
save them from the dungeon.
So, you are Osman's messenger birds.
We came to fight.
I can tell.
You have fought.
Since you are in a dungeon...
so did you. I can tell.
You got shot on your chest!
Now is time for your heart!
Tell me now.
What's Osman's plan?
How many of you are in here?
Akça Dervish.
Kumral Abdal.
And me. Isn't it enough?
Take our heads! Only thing
you'll hear from us...
the soldiers of the righteous
will triumph! You'll lose!
I'll crush you all like bugs!
Until I make you speak,
I'll shatter you.
Search everywhere.
There must be more.
Osman's plans will be ruined.
As you order.
Kumral Abdal, are you alright?
Osman is at our gates with
a formidable force.
What will we do?
We'll hand over the city.
Are we giving up, sir?
Never.
Wars aren't always won with
strong soldiers.
Sometimes, you win with
strong traps.
When Osman hears that we'll surrender,
he won't attack.
And when he lowers his sword...
we'll destroy him in the center
of Yenişehir.
What if it doesn't work and Osman
still attacks?
He won't. I know Osman.
He is food enough to keep his word.
When we surrender the city,
he won't attack.
Sir, what about our honor?
Will we surrender our honor
to win?
Rome is more important than anything.
I can sacrifice everything I have.
Even my honor.
I understand, sir.
Osman Bey's Quarters
The time will be over tomorrow.
If they don't surender...
Turgut Bey, you'll attack to the West.
I will enter from the main gates
at the East.
Aktemur, you'll enter from the North.
The women are inside. Kumral Abdal and
Master Davud have been there for a while.
They'll attack from inside and make
the South open for an attack.
Beys, you'll attack from there.
Inside and outside.
Yenişehir will be ours.
Inshallah.
But we won't touch the people.
Because we will make it home.
Now, everyone should rest.
Tomorrow, the sun will rise for conquest.
With Allah's approval and your
order, my bey.
Thank you. Thank you.
Go on.
Aygül.
Mad girl has gone completely
mad.
Where are we going?
Patience, my Cerkutay.
Patience.
My Cerkutay? I'm getting afraid.
-Aygül where are you taking me?
-How impatient are you?
Come on, move!
Don't you say ''My Aygül, I'll come
to anywhere you want with you''?
I'll come anywhere you want
with you, my Aygül.
As long as we are together.
As long as you are with me.
May Allah not test us with
longing for each other.
Humans come to the world
to be tested.
Allah tests humans with their
most beloved one.
What are you trying to say, mad girl?
Where is this place?
This is our real home.
This is where we'll come together
one day.
We are together, Aygül.
We are married.
We have children.
Aygül, where is this place?
This is where I'll come to.
I'll wait for you here.
No.
No. No!
Aygül! We'll live together.
We'll die together.
Aygül, don't die!
Let's go to our children.
Aygül!
I won't leave you that easily.
No! No!
Not that easily! No!
Aygül!
You'll come too, Cerkutay.
But not now.
We'll unite, Cerkutay.
We'll unite.
Aygül, don't go!
Don't leave me!
Aygül! Aygül!
Aygül!
Cerkutay.
Are you alright?
I was so afraid!
Did you see a nightmare?
What did you see?
Nothing!
Nothing! Nothing!
I...
should go and check around.
Ayşe Hatun. It's our time now.
When you put this on their food, they
won't open their eyes for a day.
Thank you, Ayşe Hatun. At least
the troops on the south will sleep.
The rest is ours to kill.
I prepared it last night.
Before the battle.
Come on.
Come on. It's time to renew
our oath.
With Allah's name!
A weapon and blood fits
a warrior!
Sisters compete with men
to the martyrdom!
Martyrdom is a breath to us,
and jihad is the blood in our veins.
If you are thirsty, satisfy
your heart with jihad.
Sisters, sisters!
They carry the hands of Mother Fatma!
Sisters compete with men
to the martyrdom!
Osman Bey's Quarters
Alps! Alps should be ready like they'll
move at any time.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam, my bey.
Sit now. Continue.
What did you do, Balaban?
Boran Bey requested it against
the armored enemies.
-Boran.
-My bey.
Mashallah, you did a good job.
Thank you, my bey.
It'll pierce armors and it'll
get us the city.
Inshallah. Inshallah.
My bey.
News from Romanos' messenger.
Bring him to the tent with
an eyefold.
I'll be coming soon.
Unfold it.
Speak now.
Commander Romanos and the
elders of the city have considered...
and made a decision.
If some conditions are settled,
we are ready to surrender.
What are your conditions?
The people's security of life,
property, and honor will be guaranteed.
The people's faith will not be oppressed.
And Commander Romanos
has a condition.
If his ransom is paid,
he'll be free.
Battle is a wedding to the Turks.
If we decline your conditions,
get in and hang Romanos...
who can stop us?
But we don't have a revenge vendetta.
But we do everything for Allah's words.
I accept your conditions.
Despite his actions, even Romanos
will be free.
Your properties, lives, and dignity
is under my protection.
We are grateful, Osman Bey.
I greet you as the new owner of
Yenişehir.
My bey, what if it's a trap?
So what? We've already taken
our caution.
Aygül, don't! Don't leave me.
Alright?
They said that they'll surrender
but they can't be trusted.
We'll be cautious.
Cerkutay, what do you mean?
You weren't like this even when I
was pregnant. It's not our first battle.
-What is this?
-Henna.
Did you forget it, Cerkutay?
It's a sister tradition.
We sacrifice ourselves to the homeland
before the battle.
Stay beside me!
Come on!
I thought they were surrendering.
What are they doing?
They won't surrender.
It's a trap.
Dishonored!
They have no dignity.
The dungeon is empty.
There are few soldiers.
They are bringing everyone here.
If the soldiers are stacking up,
Osman Bey will be here soon.
Come on, sisters. We'll position
to take out the ones at the roofs.
We'll go to the dungeon with Aygül.
No, I will come with you.
Cerkutay, stay here. Don't you see
all the soldiers?
We'll take care of it.
Cerkutay is right.
Bala, you are pregnant. Cerkutay
should come with you.
Good. Let's go.
May Allah bless our jihad.
Ayşe, you'll come with me.
Alaca, you'll go this way.
Seher, you'll go this way
with the sisters.
Come on.
Keep your arrows at the ready.
Come to me.
Hey, stop!
Where are you headed?
They summoned us from the dungeon
for the woundeds.
You are needed outside.
Get out.
Watch your hand, brother.
Come on.
Cerkutay, you'll take this way
and we'll take that way. Okay?
No.
We'll go together.
Cerkutay what are you talking about?
We don't have time.
We don't know whether
they are alive or not.
Aygul!
Come on Cerkutay!
Go!
My Allah.
Protect my rose.
Aygul!
What happened?
What's going on between you?
He had a nightmare.
He won't tell it,
but he is definitely under its effect.
You said he didn't tell his nightmare.
So how do you know?
Bala...
Give me your blessings.
Will you?
I will, my Aygul.
I will.
Give me your blessings too.
I do, Bala.
I do.
Let's go.
Come at once!
I need to get to my Aygul...
...after finishing you.
My Allah...
...don't test me with my sanity.
Hay Masha Allah (praise be)
Bala Hatun!
More power to you, sisters!
Thank Allah we found you safe and sound.
Aygul Hatun, behind you!
I caught you!
Any news from Osman Bey?
He is fine.
He is on his way.
Everyone get back to their missions
just like how we talked before.
Osman Bey is waiting!
Let's go!
Master Davut.
Your weapons are waiting for you
at the end of the hall.
They are on fire!
We are face to face again, Osman.
This is going to be our last meeting.
Right.
You defeated me.
You defeated the army of Rome.
Now deliver Yenisehir to me.
So that no one dies.
And Kayi will control here from now on.
Do I have any other option?
I will scratch your eyes out if
you betray my Bey!
Sisters!
What's happening?
What is happening?
O Haqq!
Masha Allah (praise be)
to my Hatun.
Allah is eternal!
Push it, brothers.
Let's push.
Push, brother!
Allah is the greatest!
Hit them, valiants!
For the sake of Allah!
Come on.
Yenisehir will be Turks' land.
Inshallah(if Allah permits), Master Davut.
Let's go.
Our brothers are fighting.
You are the new commander, Master Davut.
It's not time to talk, Kumral.
Let your hands work
instead of your tongue.
Come on.
Let's set them on fire.
We won't die before doing it.
- Let's go!
- Allah is eternal!
We won't stop until we become a martyr!
We won't stop until we plant our flag
in the center of the town!
Bala! Come on!
Come on!
Allah is eternal!
Masha Allah!
(praise be)
Wolves are on the duty!
What do you think, Cerkutay?
This is Kayi tribe!
Which gates can stop us?
Allah is eternal!
You are an army on your own, my Hatun.
Allah is righteous!
- Allah is eternal!
- Allah is righteous!
Romanos.
Kumral!
Come on Master Davut!
Are you fine, Master Davut?
Are you wounded?
Come on.
Come on!
What are you looking for.
You have nowhere to run, you infidel.
Let's see how brave you are now.
Take that dog.
Don't kill him.
Now!
Malhun.
Come on Hatuns.
May our fight be blessed.
Come on.
Ayse!
Come on!
Stop him!
Ayse!
Come on!
Do not try for nothing, Kumral.
I got ahead of you.
I will become a martyr first.
No way.
You can't leave as you wish,
Master Davut.
We will have many wars to fight.
Hold on, Master Davut.
You'll be fine Inshallah.
Am I going to die in
a foreign land, Kumral?
Have we conquered yet?
Yes.
All our alps are inside.
Thank Allah.
Give me your blessings.
I do, Master Davut.
I do.
"I bear witness that
there is no deity but, Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the messenger of Allah”.
"Verily we belong to Allah
and verily to him do we return."
My brother is a martyr now.
Come to me, ignobles!
Come to me so I can send you to hell!
Are you trying to die, mad girl?
Didn't I tell you to stay with me?
I do what you do, mad boy.
I fight for our children, grandchildren!
You won't fight
without me!
Either we live together
or we die together.
Inshallah (if Allah permits).
I had a nightmare.
Cerkutay!
Aygul!
Aygul.
Aygul, Aygul!
Cerkutay!
I wanted to settle down.
They stopped me.
I loved a rose.
I loved Aygul* (Ay=moon Gul=rose)
They broke her.
Now what's left in my hand
except for berserk?
Did you shoot with this hand?
Did you aim with those eyes?
Aygul.
Aygul!
Cerkutay.
Are you fine?
I am, I am, Aygul.
Rose of my moon, hold on.
(Ay means moon, gul means rose in Turkish)
Do not cry Cerkutay.
Don't.
Come on
Romanos.
I won't die before killing you, Osman.
There is no such sword
to kill me.
Come to me.
Where are you Aygul?
The sword to kill you is in my hands.
Someday...
...you'll breed will vanish.
Both you and your breed will die.
We're all going to die, but...
...Turks' state will stay forever.
Take that dog's head.
Thank my Creator!
Thanks a lot.
Thank you, Creator!
Thank Him.
Valiants, I appreciate your bravery!
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah
Thank you, Osman Bey. You made this city
a homeland to Turks, to us.
No, we took the homeland from our
ancestors.
But those who will enlarge it are our
children.
Son...
...draw your sword.
This won't go down until the world is
ours, my Bey!
Praise be!
-My Bey.
-Valiants.
Romanos convinced the people of
disobedience.
They neither speak nor surrender.
They didn't let us close, my Bey.
We didn't make a move without your
order.
What should we do, my Bey?
So, they paint us badly.
In that case, it is time to show them
the truth.
They won't believe us, my Bey.
They are afraid.
Right.
Is the Priest here?
He is, my Bey.
Since they don't believe us...
...one of them will speak then.
Call the Priest.
Gather everyone in the square.
-Yes, my Bey.
-Come on.
Why?
Why did you do this?
Father is a mountain, Cerkutay.
A child can't be without a father.
So that you be a mountain to our children.
No! No! No! I told you!
We will either live together or die
together.
No, Aygül! No!
You will get up now and we will go to
Kumral Abdal.
He will treat you.
Cerkutay, do you remember the dream you
had?
I dreamed that too.
I saw where I am going, Cerkutay.
No, no! Don't leave me without you!
Don't talk like death is the end,
Cerkutay.
We will meet in the afterlife.
I will wait.
But don't come early, come in time.
Don't go, Aygül! Don't go, Aygül!
Don't go, Aygül!
I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah, and I bear witness...
...that Muhammad (PBUH) is the
servant and Messenger of Allah.
Aygül! Mad girl!
Aygül!
Wake up! Wake up!
Aygül! Aygül!
I don't want it!
I don't want it! We will never surrender!
Children, children.
Come here. Come here boy!
Son.
People!
Come here!
We didn't come here to kill, on the
contrary, we came to make it live!
We had never drawn our swords at an
innococent!
And we never will!
We had never made a child cry.
And we won't!
You are the same as Söğüt and İnegöl
people to me.
Come on, son. Go to your mother.
Come on.
Come on, go.
Your places of worship will be repaired.
You will continue your trade.
And your properties will still be yours.
No one will touch them.
I know your taxes are expensive.
We will decrease them as well.
Your lives and your properties are
entrusted to me from now on.
But if there are still people who have
doubts and fear me...
...you can ask the Priest about us.
He is your co-religionist and religious
leader.
He knows you and you know him.
You can open your hearts to him freely.
There you go.
Alps.
Come on.
May Jesus be with you my sisters and
brothers.
I understand your fears.
However, I witnessed every word of Osman
Bey.
Giving up the city is the best for you.
And later on, trusting me.
You will see nothing in your city except
justice and mercy.
I assure you.
Master Davut.
The architect of many conquests...
...now...
...became a martyr in the land of Turk.
May his martyrdom be blessed.
-Amen!
His name will go on as long as the lands
of Turks...
...exist.
Cerkutay!
Aygül!
What will I do now?
Cerkutay.
-Amen.
Amen.
Raise your head.
This is neither an end nor a defeat.
This is a new beginning for all of us.
People!
Yeni Şehir will be the capital of Kayı
from now on!
Together we will restore these lands
where the hearts of Turks...
...and Islam will beat.
Therefore, your life...
... your property...
...and your honor...
...are entrusted to me!
A state is founded on Justice.
And as long as there is justice...
...the state will remain.
Thus, your rights are also entrusted to
us.
You will live in prosperity without
discrimination of religion...
...and nationality.
But know that...
...I am not your owner.
I am only...
...the owner of the sword of justice.
When I become dust one day...
...what will remain will be my poor tent
...
...my wretched horse...
...and my sword that dispenses justice.
We don't forget where we came from...
...and why.
But we always keep in mind where we
are going.
Our way is the way of Allah.
It is the world order that leads us to
that path.
Where the road takes us is the word
of Allah.
We must make moves for that road.
We must take action.
Just like how our ancestors came to these
lands and made them a home...
...we will do the same.
We will walk towards the future.
Our next home will be...
...Yeni Şehir.
Yeni Şehir will open many doors of
conquest for us.
It will make us dominate the world.
Time is like a river, it flows.
We will be the bed of that river.
We will build a state that will last
forever.
It will be such a state that it will...
...fly the flag of Islam around the whole
world.
It will be such a state that it will...
...spread justice to the whole world.
It will be such a state that...
....it will always remain!
-Allah is one!
Allah is one!
I brought Osman Bey's greetings, Ali Bey.
Thank you!
I am glad you came, valiant.
We could thankfully conquer Yeni Şehir.
Osman Bey is having a feast.
He expects you too.
Praise be!
Such blessed news!
Right! Osman Bey doesn't know how to
stop.
Praise be! Praise be!
We are honored to accept Osman Bey's
invitation.
Tell him that we will come, valiant.
Thank you.
Oh, my Allah, mightiest of all!
You granted us many conquests.
On this land you granted us...
...many valiants and many sisters...
...bled.
Gündüz Bey!
Osman!
Mother!
-Mother!
Göktuğ!
Cerkutay!
I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah, and I bear witness that...
...Muhammad (PBUH) is the servant
and Messenger of Allah.
My Allah you order in your book...
...not to call the martyrs dead.
May you keep our martyrs together with
our prophets and your good servants.
Accept them into your heaven with those
who were martyred in Badr and Uhud.
Amen.
Sons.
We have something to tell you, father.
First Selvi...
...now Aygül.
I don't know which one to cry for.
My sister died before finding out what the
traitor she called her husband had done.
It wouldn't be better if she did, Malhun.
She would have gotten worse.
Every cloud has a silver lining.
Maybe this was better for her.
Right.
Selvi, Aygül...
...Gonca.
And many other sisters who were martyred.
They walked to Allah...
...for a blessed cause.
My Aygül knew...
...where she was going before.
But...
...how will we tell this to her children?
We will be strong, my Ayşe.
We will be strong.
Let's not cry for them anymore and
make them uneasy.
Hatuns.
Didn't we risk dying on our cause's way...
...the first day we laid our hands on our
swords?
Didn't we get these hennas for this
reason?
Now...
...we send our blessings...
...to every martyr who opened the way
for the conquest.
Amen.
Allah is one.
May peace be upon you.
My Rabb.
In the name of Allah.
Here you go sons.
Enjoy.
Yes, sons.
Tell me.
My Bey father.
We thought of something with Alaaddin.
But first, we ask for your blessing.
Tell me.
We learned that a state is established
in hardships.
But they go down because of wars
for the throne...
...jealousies and evil.
Thus, we want to be the two wings
of the state you'll establish.
We want to remain together, father.
If you'll let me...
...I'd like to serve the state with my
knowledge.
And for this, I want to go to Konya.
To a madrasa.
My Alaaddin!
Praise be! Praise be!
What about you, my Orhan?
I want to fight by your side.
I want to have your back with my sword,
father.
So...
...sons...
...you want to rule together.
Just like...
...Kültigin and Bilge Khan.
Praise be to my valiants!
Praise be!
Now...
...listen to me carefully.
Sons...
... a state is a two-winged bird.
One of the wings is a sword...
...and the other is knowledge and wisdom.
But...
...if one of these wings is missing...
...this bird can't fly.
How can a bird that can't fly rule
the world?
How can it spread justice to the world?
Sons...
...you are the two wings of that bird.
The state will live with you.
And you will live with the state.
My lions!
İnegöl Castle
I came, Gündüz.
You might say it is late.
Of course, you are right.
I couldn't come before.
Now I came.
Ayşe!
Gündüz!
I came to say what
I couldn't say...
...to your face.
I didn't bury only you in this land,
Gündüz.
I buried my Işık too.
I was in the dark.
I couldn't speak.
Every day became night since you left.
But I won't cry.
You told me not to. So, I won't cry.
But now.
The sun is rising again.
Again.
Gündüz.
Gündüz Bey.
We are having another child.
Another child from you...
...to me.
But without you...
...longing for you...
You were so happy when you found out I was
pregnant with Aktemur.
Your eyes smiled at me.
I wish you were here with me now
so that...
...I could tell you these while looking
at your pretty eyes.
And you would tell me...
...''My Ayşe, light of my eye.''
I couldn't save you, Gündüz!
I couldn't save you.
No.
Don't think I am ungrateful.
Could I ever be?
No.
You...
...made İnegöl home for us.
You died for us.
I will raise children who will take care
of your legacy.
Gündüz Bey's sons...
...will be befitting Gündüz Bey.
My Malhun.
Thanks to Allah that...
...he granted us our every goal.
Thankfully, my Osman.
With the will of Allah and...
...with the strength of you and those
under your command.
No, don't spare yourself.
A state lives with the mothers.
If I didn't have a mother like you
behind me...
...my family...
...it'd be nothing like this.
Your love warms my heart, my Osman.
There is the fire of our love in my heart.
I would go anywhere with you, Osman Bey.
My brave hatun!
As long as I have my family behind me...
...nothing can decrease my strength,
thankfully.
I hope our children will be brave, honest
...
...and faithful like you.
What makes a son a Bey is his mother.
They will be as you raise them.
But...
...I hope they will have your patience and
wisdom so that...
...our state rules the whole world.
But...
... who can stand against those who have
a mother like you?
Praise be!
Praise be! Osman Bey built his dream
in this tribe.
Now, he makes conquests after conquests.
Right.
Avoiding war doesn't get anything to Beys.
War will continue so that...
...the tribe grows.
Conquest is the lifeblood of Turks.
He will drink and drink so that the Turks
grow.
The state Osman Bey will establish will be
...
...a hope for all Turkmens.
Supporting his cause is an honor for
Çobanoğlu.
Since you are this thirsty for conquest...
...you will stay with Osman Bey.
You will be under his command.
Guzzle the lifeblood, son.
Brother...
...you fought many wars with my father.
When do you think I can fight the
infidels?
I was impatient too.
But time flies by.
One day you'll look and see a sword
in your hand.
I hope so, brother.
My mother is coming.
Mother!
Why are you carrying these while there are
many hatuns?
You see, Ayşe?
They grew up and don't let us do
hardwork.
Praise be! Praise be!
-Thankfully.
My Ahmed sent news. He is coming back.
They can't make it today but they
will be here tomorrow, I hope.
I hope so.
Come on.
How is Konya?
-Is its wind hard?
-It is, my Sheik.
It is so hard that the seeds of the state
get dispersed around the world by it.
This is where the Turkish state will
flourish.
Allah is the one who blows the wind and
makes the seed grow.
Tell me about my daughter,
my grandchildren, Dursun.
They pray for your health, my Sheik.
I've prepared their convoys.
The reunion is soon.
They will come.
Thankfully! Thankfully!
Did you say goodbye to your students?
I left the professorship behind me.
Now...
...I am a messenger who will convey Sultan
Alaaddin's trust to Osman Bey.
I am ready for the duty my Bey
assigned me.
Your duty is already ready, Dursun.
We need skills in pen as much as we do
in sword.
Obviously, your coming is blessed.
The signs he brings are the signs of
the state to be established.
The pen is here.
The state is near, right brother?
Brothers...
...you keep what you took by sword with
knowledge.
You are right.
Come on, let's go to Osman Bey.
From now on...
...just like Bilecik, İnegöl...
...and the whole Hisar...
...Yeni Şehir is the property of Kayı.
We know that our people are bigger
than Kayı.
And we will make a move according to
the greatness.
In these lands where the flag of Islam
flies...
...there will be no cruelty or injustice!
Welcome.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
These are Sultan Alaaddin's signs to Osman
Bey.
He sent you a fast and robust horse.
He tells you not to stop the conquests.
In the name of Allah.
He sent Quran which was written by skilled
calligraphers.
He tells you to always order by Quran.
In the name of Allah.
He sent you the sharpest sword.
So that the oppressors can't stand against
you.
Sultan congratulates your conquest,
Osman Bey.
Thank him.
And thank you, Dursun Faki.
Conquests are for the sake of Turks
and Islam.
Sultan is opening our way for us.
We will walk it as long as we are alive.
We won't stop until the world feels small
to us.
Islam is the religion of justice.
And we will spread this religion to
the whole world!
Wherever there is cruelty and injustice...
...we will hit it with the sword of
justice!
Now our goal is...
...Bursa on one hand...
...and İznik on the other hand!
Yeni Şehir will be our capital.
From now on...
...it will be our headquarter for
the conquests!
My Beys!
My brothers!
We get our power...
...from our cause!
But we get our strength from those...
...who always support us...
...and are no different from the men
of Kayı, our Hatuns!
From our Alps!
From our valiants whose hearts are made of
steel!
From our beys who fill their flags with
winds!
As long as the Turks have you...
...no one can stop us!
Until the sky goes down...
...and the earth breaks down...
...who can stop you?
Not spreading our cause to the whole world
...
...is haram to us!
Allah is the greatest!
End of season 3
See you on the next season!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com